prizegrab.com 2017-06-29

# Privacy Policy

REVISION DATE: 05/24/15

Thank you for visiting www.prizegrab.com and participating in our Sponsored Sweepstakes. We take your privacy seriously, which is why we developed this privacy policy to explain our online information collection and use practices. This Policy is limited solely to online transactions and do not apply to any off line privacy rights or obligations, data collection and data transfers. 

### Collection of Information.

We collect personal data from our users during the initial registration process, notification process and when users contact us for any reason. Thus, users can determine to some extent what information they wish to provide to us. In addition to the initial registration process, we may, from time to time, ask users to answer surveys about our or third party products and services. We gather this data in order to better understand our users' interests and provide them with relevant offers and information.

Through the use of "cookies" and "pixel tags"(both described below) and online survey and registration forms, we may collect personal data including name, address, email address, phone or mobile number. We may also collect demographic information such as age, gender, income level or technical information such as IP address, domain name, email address, site traffic, where you visited before or after visiting our website.

### Collection of Technology Information.

As stated above, we collect technology information through cookies and pixel tags. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your web browser software on your computer's hard drive or temporarily in your computer's memory. The use of cookies is now an industry standard, and users will find them on most major websites. We may place and store cookies on a user's hard drive. Cookies can collect the information we noted above. Cookies enable us to recognize you and personalize your viewing experience on our website. For example, we use cookies to track site usage and traffic patterns, add advertisements for goods or services that we think may interest you, and estimate the audience size. We also use cookies to store user names and information that are supplied at registration. Although most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, if you prefer, you can decline the placement of a cookie on your hard drive by using the appropriate feature(s) of your web browser software to delete or block the cookie. Please note that certain areas on our Website will not function properly if your web browser does not accept cookies. Third party advertisers and publishers may place cookies on your computer by or through our Website. We have no access or control of third party cookies. However, you may block or remove them in the same manner as our cookies through your browser settings.

"Pixel tracking" is a common process which may be used in connection with advertisements on the Website. Pixel tags that are not visible to the user of the Website and consist of a few lines of computer coding. Pixels are tracking measures to determine the effectiveness of advertisements and compiles aggregate and specific usage statistics. A "pixel tag" is an invisible tag placed on certain pages of the Websites you may visit and is used to track an individual user's activity. We may access these pixel tags to identify activity and interests that may allow us to better match our offers with your interests. For example, if you visit our Website from an advertisement on another website, the pixel tag will allow us to track that this advertisement brought you to us. If you visit our website and we link you to another website we are able to determine that you were sent to and/or transacted business with a third party website. This data is collected for use in our marketing and research. Personally identifiable information about you is not collected by the third party advertising company, nor is any tracking information generated from the pixel tag allowed to be used by them for any other purpose other than to report website activity to us.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click data. We use this information, which does not identify you directly to analyze trends, administer the website, track your movements around our website and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

We may use Google Analytics on parts of our Website. If you prefer to not have your data used by Google Analytics you may visit the Google Analytics [opt-out page ](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)and install the add-on for your browser.

The third party advertisers, vendors and ad networks may also use cookies to show advertisements to you. These third-party vendors may include Google DoubleClick, Media.net, and/or other ad networks. Each network uses cookies to enable it to serve ads to you based on your visit to our Website and/or other websites on the Internet. You may opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting aboutads.info at any time.

### Sharing Information With Third Parties.

We share your personal information with the Sponsor of the Sweepstakes so that they may contact you if you win or if there is an issue with your entry. We may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties. We will also release specific personal information about you if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

In the event of a merger, acquisition, or change of control of our company, your information would be considered a business asset and would be disclosed and transferred. We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We may also disclose personal information as required by law or to protect the safety and security of our users. Finally we will use your information to deliver our own commercial offers to you. 

### Opt Out rights.

Receiving email messages from us or anyone we share your information with is optional. As noted earlier, the collection, use, and distribution of personal data helps us create a more personalized, relevant, and intelligent web service for our users. While some basic data is necessary to provide certain services, such as entry into the sweepstakes, there are some cases where the submission of information is optional. All users who provide their Information to PrizeGrab.com may modify and correct such Information through their personal profile or by contacting us [ here.](https://prizegrab.com/contact)

But if you are receiving offers from other companies, you may follow the simple opt-out procedure contained in each email at the bottom of the email. If you are receiving our emails and no longer wish to receive such communications, simply follow the "unsubscribe" instructions that appear in every one of our emails, or contact us at PrizeGrab.com, 548 Market St #77649 San Francisco, CA 94104-5401 

### No Control of Third Party Links or Privacy Practices.

To the extent hyperlinks or banner advertisements incorporating hyperlinks are used on our website which provide you access to third party websites, you should be aware that these third party web sites are not controlled by us and, therefore, are not subject to this privacy policy. We recommend that you check the privacy policies of the websites to see how your personal information will be used and how to opt-out.

### Security of Information.

We have implemented a number of security features throughout our website and on the servers that hold all the collected data that are intended to prevent the unauthorized release of or access to the user information we collect online. The database is firewall protected and held in a secure location. Only authorized personnel have access to any stored personal information we collect from our users. However, e-mail is not encrypted and is not considered a secure means of transmitting any sensitive data. As such, the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted over the Internet cannot be 100% guaranteed. Therefore we are not responsible or liable for illegal interception of personal data by unknown third parties. 

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your Prizegrab Login ID and Password. We maintain rules to help prevent others from guessing your password. We recommend that you change your Password frequently. If you believe that they have been stolen or been made known to others, you must contact us immediately via our Contact form found on our Help page at [http://www.prizegrab.com/contact](https://www.prizegrab.com/contact) but in any event you should change your password immediately via the Service. We are not responsible if someone else accesses your account through Registration Information they have obtained from you or through a violation by you of this Privacy and Security Policy or the Prizegrab.com Terms of Use.

### Personal information of Children or Persons residing outside the US

We do not target or direct collection of information from children under the age of thirteen. We do not intend to collect personal data from individuals under the age of 18 or non-US citizens. If we receive actual notice that a child under the age of thirteen has provided personal data to us or a resident from a country outside the United States, we will use reasonable efforts to remove such information from our database.

### California Privacy Rights:

The following information for California residents covers on-line (internet) and off-line (direct mail) information sharing activities. From time to time we may share or exchange marketing information about you with other companies so they may contact you about products and services that may interest you. If you do not want your name passed on to other companies for the purpose of receiving marketing offers, please contact us at PrizeGrab.com, 548 Market St #77649 San Francisco, CA 94104-5401 and we will respect your wishes. Please make sure to provide both your email address and full name, mailing address, city, state and zip code information if you wish your request to apply to both on-line and off-line marketing information sharing. In addition, you should know that we do not respond to do-not-track cookies or other do-not-track technology.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we make material changes to our policy, we will post a prominent notice on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Please review this Privacy Policy from time to time so that you will be apprised of any changes.

### Questions and Contact Information.

If you have any questions or comments regarding this privacy policy or the use of personal data, please contact us at PrizeGrab.com, 548 Market St #77649 San Francisco, CA 94104-5401 

NO PURCHASE NECESSARY. A purchase of payment of any kind will not increase your chances of winning. You do not need to click ads in order to enter or win. Void where prohibited. Sponsored by Prizegrab.com. See Official Rules. 

The third-party product names, logos, brands, and trademarks shown on this website are the property of their respective owners. These companies are not affiliated with PrizeGrab.com and do not sponsor or endorse any sweepstakes.
